Charlene Drew Jarvis 131
DCPL Special Collections - MLK Library
Charlene Drew Jarvis Papers
1978-2014
DCPL Special Collections - MLK Library
Jarvis, Charlene Drew
131
18 cubic feet; 18 boxes
18 Boxes
Charlene Drew Jarvis was elected to D.C.'s City Council in 1979 and remained on the council until 2000. While on the council she chaired the Committee on Economic Development and the Committee on Finance and Revenue during D.C.'s traumatic financial times. In 1992, Drew Jarvis became the national co-chair of the Clinton/Gore campaign. In 1993, she was appointed by Clinton to serve on the National Institute of Health Mental Health Advisory Council. Documents include biographical information, brochures, campaign materials, correspondence, contact lists, council files, Board of Elections and Ethics files, mailings, programs, photographs, publications, speeches, and audiovisual recordings of public appearances.
Biographical / Historical
Charlene Drew Jarvis was born at Howard University Hospital on July 31, 1941 to Lenore and Dr. Charles Drew. Her father was famed surgeon and pioneer in blood plasma research at Howard University medical school. Drew Jarvis attended Mott Elementary, Banneker Middle and Roosevelt High School. She went on to earn a B.A. from Oberlin College, an M.A. from Howard University and a PhD in Neuropsychology from the University of Maryland. She continued in science research until the late 1970s. Drew Jarvis was elected to D.C.'s City Council in 1979 and remained on the council until 2000. While on the council she chaired the Committee on Economic Development and the Committee on Finance and Revenue during D.C.'s traumatic financial times. In 1992, Drew Jarvis became the national co-chair of the Clinton/Gore campaign. In 1993, she was appointed by Clinton to serve on the National Institute of Health Mental Health Advisory Council. During her tenure on the council, she ran for mayor in 1996. In 1996, she was named president of Southeastern University and remained in the position until 2009.
Scope and Contents
The Charlene Drew Jarvis papers document her campaign for city council, her time as national co-chair for the Clinton/Gore presidential campaign, and her work on on the National Institute of Health Mental Health Advisory Council. Documents include biographical information, brochures, campaign materials, correspondence, contact lists, council files, Board of Elections and Ethics files, mailings, programs, photographs, publications, speeches, and audiovisual recordings of public appearances.
Women; Political campaigns; Politicians; Politics and government; Ephemera; Photographs; Speeches, addresses, etc; Organizational Records; Mental health; District of Columbia. City Council; African Americans
- Series 1
  - Brochures: Various, 1992-1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Brochures: Various, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Brochures: Campaign, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Brochures: Various, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Brochures: Campaign, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Brochures: Campaign, 1992-1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Brochures: Chamber's Choice Awards, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Publications: Articles by or about Charlene Drew Jarvis, 1984-1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Publications: Various, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Publications: The Jarvis Report, 1996-1999 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Publications: Articles by or about Charlene Drew Jarvis, 1990-1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Publications: The Renaissance, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Publications: The Council of the District of Columbia 1 of 2, 1991-1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Publications: The Council of the District of Columbia 2 of 2, 1991-1997 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Publications: Washington Magazines, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Publications: Various, 1992-1998 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Publications: Various, 1998-2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Publications: Articles by or about Charlene Drew Jarvis, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Publications: George Washington University Commencement 1 of 2, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Publications: George Washington University Commencement 2 of 2, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Publications: Magazines, 2000-2009 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Publications: Magazines, 2011-2013 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Publications: Articles about Charlene Drew Jarvis, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Publications: Political Campaign Fundraiser, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Cards and Invitations, 2010-2014 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Cards and Invitations, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Cards and Invitations 1 of 2, 2000-2004 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Cards and Invitations 2 of 2, 2000-2004 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Cards and Invitations 1 of 2, 1990-1999 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Cards and Invitations 2 of 2, 1990-1999 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Cards and Invitations, 1985-1989 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Invitations: White House, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Mailings: Various, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Mailings: Campaign - Various, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Mailings: Campaign, 1982-1989 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Mailings: Campaign, 1992-1999 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Flyers: Campaign, 1992-1996 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Handwritten Notes, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Awards, 1982-2013 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Speeches: Charlene Drew Jarvis at Drew University, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Speeches: Councilmember Charlene Drew Jarvis, 1986-1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Speeches: Charlene Drew Jarvis, 1995-1999 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Speeches: Various Speakers, 1993-1998 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Speeches: Charlene Drew Jarvis Mayoral Campaign, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Speeches: Various Speakers, 2002-2012 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Speeches: Charlene Drew Jarvis University Speeches, 2006-2015 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Speeches: Charlene Drew Jarvis Various Speeches, 2002-2014 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Speeches: Charlene Drew Jarvis "Living a Life of Truth and Faith" Baccalaureate Ceremony - George Washington University, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Speeches: Charlene Drew Jarvis Commencement Speeches, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Flyers: Charlene Drew Jarvis Birthday Celebration, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Flyers: White House, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Flyers: Our Community for Jarvis, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Flyers: Charlene Drew Jarvis Campaign, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Flyers: Events for Charlene Drew Jarvis, 1991-1996 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Flyers: Various, 1990-1999 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Flyers: Charlene Drew Jarvis Campaign, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Flyers: Events for Charlene Drew Jarvis, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Flyers: Various, 2000-2014 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Flyers: Campaign - Various, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Programs: Charlene Drew Jarvis Ward 4 Office Opening, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Programs: Georgia Avenue Day, 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Programs: Presidential Campaigns, 1981-1987 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Programs: Various, 1982-1988 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Programs: White House 1 of 2, 1993-1999 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Programs: White House 2 of 2, 1993-1999 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Programs: District of Columbia Government, 1990-1999 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Programs: Events with Charlene Drew Jarvis, 1990-1999 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Programs: Various 1 of 2, 1993-1999 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Programs: Various 2 of 2, 1993-1999 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Programs: White House, 2000-2009 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Programs: Events with Charlene Drew Jarvis 1 of 2, 2000-2007 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Programs: Events with Charlene Drew Jarvis 1 of 2, 2000-2007 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Programs: Various, 2000-2008 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Programs: Events with Charlene Drew Jarvis, 2010-2014 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Programs: District of Columbia Events, 2011-2014 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Programs: Various, 2010-2014 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Programs: Events with Charlene Drew Jarvis, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Southeastern University, 2002-2007 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Southeastern University, 1996-1999 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Handouts: Convention Center, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Mailings: Various, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Mailings: Campaign, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Mailings: Campaign, 1998-1992 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Mailings: Clinton/Gore Campaign, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Contact Lists: Political Campaigns 1 of 2, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Contact Lists: Political Campaigns 2 of 2, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Contact Lists: Newsletters, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Contact Lists: Handwritten Lists, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Contact Lists: University Club of Washington D.C., 2003 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Contact Lists: Candidates and Councilmembers, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Council of the District of Columbia: Information about how the Council functions, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Council of the District of Columbia: Legislation 1 of 3, 1994-2002 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Council of the District of Columbia: Legislation 2 of 3, 1994-2002 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Council of the District of Columbia: Legislation 2 of 3, 1994-2002 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Council of the District of Columbia: Photographs, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Campaign Materials: Bring Back Dave Clarke Committee, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Campaign Materials: Charlene Drew Jarvis Campaign Call List, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Campaign Materials: Contact Lists, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Campaign Materials: Charlene Drew Jarvis Campaign for Mayor Position Statements, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Campaign Materials: Charlene Drew Jarvis Mayoral Campaign Position Statements, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Campaign Materials: Charlene Drew Jarvis Informational Handouts, 1993-2000 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Campaign Materials: Charlene Drew Jarvis Mayoral Campaign Gay and Lesbian Community Position, 1990-2000 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Campaign Materials: Charlene Drew Mayoral Campaign Positions Binder, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Campaign Materials: Charlene Drew Jarvis Mayoral Campaigns 1 of 2, 1996-2000 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Campaign Materials: Charlene Drew Jarvis Mayoral Campaigns 2 of 2, 1996-2000 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Campaign Materials: Clinton Gore Campaign, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Campaign Materials: Charlene Drew Jarvis Mayoral Campaign 1 of 2, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Campaign Materials: Charlene Drew Jarvis Mayoral Campaign 2 of 2, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Campaign Materials: Various Charlene Drew Jarvis Campaign Materials, 1978-2003 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Campaign Materials: Jeffrey Gildenhorn for Mayor Campaign, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Forms: District of Columbia Campaign Forms, 1992-1996 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Forms: Various, 1993-2002 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Forms: Office of Campaign Finance, undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Forms: Charlene Drew Jarvis Campaigns, undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - News Releases: Charlene Drew Jarvis Campaigns, undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - News Releases: Charlene Drew Jarvis Campaigns and as a Councilmember, 1986-1993 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - New Releases: Various, 1993-1998 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Memorandums: Charlene Drew Jarvis Office and Campaign, 1990-1998 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Memorandums: Various, 1989-1998 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Questionnaires: Charlene Drew Jarvis Mayoral Campaign, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Questionnaires: Charlene Drew Jarvis Campaign for Council Chair, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Questionnaires: Charlene Drew Jarvis District of Columbia Council Member Campaign, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Questionnaires: Various, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - District of Columbia Board of Elections and Ethics: Voter Registration, 1993-1998 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - District of Columbia Board of Elections and Ethics: Election Results and Returns, 1990-2000 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - District of Columbia Board of Elections and Ethics: Office of Campaign Finance, 1996-2003 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - District of Columbia Board of Elections and Ethics: Candidacy and Position Information, 1993-2000 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence: Council of the District of Columbia, 1990-1996 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Various, 1990-1999 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Various, 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Council of the District of Columbia, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Council of the District of Columbia, 2000-2007 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Council of the District of Columbia 1 of 2, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Council of the District of Columbia 2 of 2, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Council of the District of Columbia, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Campaign, 2000-2003 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: White House, 1992-2009 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Various, 2000-2008 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Campaign, 1996-1998 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Campaign, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Campaign, 1990-1995 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Campaign, 1982-1987 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Biographies: Charlene Drew Jarvis 1 of 2, 1992-2002 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Biographies: Charlene Drew Jarvis 2 of 2, 1992-2002 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Biographies: Various, 1994-2010 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Biographies: Torches of Howard Calendar, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous: American Council on Education Report on Women Presidents in Higher Education, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous: Poetry, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous: District of Columbia State Job Training Coordinating Council/ Private Industry Council, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous: Ward 4 Community Meeting Packet, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous: Schedules, 1993-2001 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous: Closing Ceremony Packets, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous: Charlene Drew Jarvis Campaign and Office Budgets, 1992-1998 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous: Workforce Investments Act of 1998 Overview (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous: White House Thank You Mailings, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous: U.S. House of Representative Committee on Government Reform and Oversight: Charlene Drew Jarvis Testimony, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous: Government of the District of Columbia: Department of Public Works, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous: Loose Printed Materials, 1994-2000 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Ward Four December "86" Gala Photo Album, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Charlene Drew Jarvis Birthday Campaign Fundraiser Ward 4 Re-Election Photo Album, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Andromeda Anniversary Photo Album, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Birthday Celebration and Auction For Councilmember Charlene Drew Jarvis Photo Album, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Photos showing Ward 4 Georgia Avenue Event Photo Album, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Reunion/bus/tour Photo Album, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Charlene Drew Jarvis Tenth Anniversary Celebration/Georgia Avenue Day Parade Photo Album, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Celebration for Deputy Chief Kais Coligan Photo Album, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Photos of Industrial Bank of Washington Holiday event Photo Album, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Tribute to Martin Luther King Jr. Photo Album, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Photos of Backyard Tea Party 1 Photo Album, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Photos of Florida A and M University Comencement Ceremony Photo Album, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Photos of DC Heritage Tourism Coalition Speech Photo Album, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Photos of Backyard Tea Party 2 Photo Album, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Photos of Jarvis for Mayor Event Photo Album, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Photos of Various Mayoral Campaign Appearances Photo Album, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - The Al Gore Story Video Tape, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Demo: Commencement - 1998 Video Tape (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Short Version of Tribute "Celebrate the Legacy" Video Tape, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Southwest: Our Home, Our Future Southwest Neighborhood Assembly, 1998 Video Tape (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Washington D.C. City Council Council of the Whole 12/15/2000 Tape 1 of 2 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Washington D.C. City Council Council of the Whole 12/15/2000 Tape 2 of 2 Video Tape (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Celebrate the Legacy Video Tape, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Mayoral Forum Charlene Drew Jarvis Video Tape, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Washington D.C. City Council Council of the Whole 12/19/2000 Tape 1 of 2 Video Tape (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Washington D.C. City Council Council of the Whole 12/19/2000 Tape 2 of 2 Video Tape (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Washington Convention Center Video Tape, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Duke Ellington's Washington Video Tape, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - The Other Side of Washington Volume 2 of 5 Video Tape, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Budget Hearing Committee on the Judiciary Rolark Video Tape, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - CBS Evening News Video Tape, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Good Morning Washington: Norton Tax Bill Video Tape, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Discovery Health Channels Medical Honors Awards Show Video Tape, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - National Political Congress of Black Women Inc. Annual Awards Brunch Part 1 Video Tape, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - National Political Congress of Black Women Inc. Annual Awards Brunch Part 2 Video Tape, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Public Roundtable- Tax Revenue Video Tape 2-Mar, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Lewis Marshall Presents Charlene Drew Jarvis Video Tape, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Economic Development Committee Budget Hearing Video Tape, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Legislation Session Re: Property Tax Video Tape, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Washington Business Week Video Tape, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - The D.C. Community Humanities Council: In Search of Common Ground Video Tape, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - D.C. Chamber of Commerce Awards Dinner/ The MCI Center: The Heart of the City Video Tape, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Worldnet: Charlene Drew Jarvis Video Tape, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Southeastern University "Don't Wait Any Longer" Video Tape, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Capstone Charlene Drew Jarvis, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Expanding Small Business Opportunities for Bankers Video Tape, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - M's Table Video Tape, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - "From Dreams to Reality: A Tribute to Minority Inventors" Video Tape, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - "Cash Cow Rev. w/Bell Nat'l" "Education Scroll Rev. w/ Big Bell National" Video Tape, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Hearing on the Council Video Tape, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Georgetown Heritage Trust Townhall Meeting Video Tape, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - DC Chamber of Commerce Washington D.C. "Experience the Opportunities" Video Tape, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Ask the Doctor at America's Health Network: Hosted by Winnie King Video Tape, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - National Institute of Mental Health ABC Prime Time Video Tape, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Worldnet: Charlene Drew Jarvis Video Tape, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Neighborhood Action Summit Video Tape, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - "Washington DC: The Word Within" Video Tape, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - RFK Stadium and the D.C. Armory Video Tape, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Howard University Hospital "The 1862 Society" Legacy of Leadership Video Tape, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - NBC4 Moments We Remember Video Tape, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - ABC "Nightline:" Dr. E Katz - Dr. Charlene Drew Jarvis- need for minority volunteer donors Video Tape, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - "Ivan Lee" Live at Five Video Tape, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - The Man from Hope Video Tape, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Club House and Republic Dance 91 Video Tape, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Wall Street Week Tax Special: The New Tax Law and You Video Tape, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Charles Woods Documentary/Advertisement Video Tape, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Contrary to Love Families Video Tape, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - The Year in Review: Black History - 1991 Video Tape (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - The Business Connection Video Tape, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Kinematin Incorporation: An Introduction Video Tape, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - A Life-Saving Choice: Nancy Wilson, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Mae Hurd's Birthday Party Video Tape, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Education Library Recreation Hearing, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - National Institute of Health "Blood Bank PSA" Version 1and 2 Video Tape, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - By The People, For the People: The Economic Resurgence of Washington, D.C. Video Tape, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Washington Tennis and Education Foundation "Changing Children's Lives" Video Tape, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Ward 4 Presents Mayor Williams Video Tape, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - D.C. Central Kitchen- Food Service Job Training Program - ABC News- Nightline: Second Helpings Video Tape, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - City Council Legislative Session Video Tape, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - ABC "Nightline:" Dr. E Katz - Dr. Charlene Drew Jarvis- need for minority volunteer donors Video Tape, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - ABC "Nightline:" Dr. E Katz - Dr. Charlene Drew Jarvis- need for minority volunteer donors Video Tape, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - ABC "Nightline:" Dr. E Katz - Dr. Charlene Drew Jarvis- need for minority volunteer donors Video Tape, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - ABC "Nightline:" Dr. E Katz - Dr. Charlene Drew Jarvis- need for minority volunteer donors Video Tape, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Charlene Drew Jarvis Telecommunications weeks of 6/17 Video Tape, undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Hospitality with the Heart Video Tape, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Jarvis for Mayor 1) Supporters Video Tape, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Audit Briefing Video Tape, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - The "Y"Guys: The Story of the First African-American YMCA in the Nation Video Tape, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - 48 Hours Video Video Tape, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Charlene Drew Jarvis Evening Exchange Video Tape, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Worldnet Norton - Williams Video Tape, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - "Susan King Cover Story" News 7 Late Edition Video Tape, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - WETA Action Series: Housing Video Tape, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Montgomery County Council Hearing on moving soup kitchen towards D.C. Video Tape, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Viewpoint 94-27 Video Tape, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - D.C. Today Video Tape, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Campaign 90' Video Tape, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - ABC "Nightline:" Dr. E Katz - Dr. Charlene Drew Jarvis- need for minority volunteer donors Video Tape, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Changing Roles… During Recessionary Times Video Tape, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - ABC "Nightline:" Dr. E Katz - Dr. Charlene Drew Jarvis- need for minority volunteer donors Video Tape, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Local Edition Video Tape, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - "Charlene Drew Jarvis" Eyewitness News Video Tape, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Democratic Convention Video Tape, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Clinton Walking Tour Georgia Avenue Video Tape, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - STS-44 Post Flight Press Conference Video Tape, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Jarvis "Life Choices" Video Tape, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Charlene Drew Jarvis Mayoral Announcement National Press Club Video Tape, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Woman to Woman TV Program with Dr. Rhonda Kelley: African Americans Uniting for Life Video Tape, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - African Americans Uniting for Life: New Orleans TV Coverage Video Tape, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Viewpoint 94-27 Video Tape, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Black History Banquet Video Tape, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - WHMM-TV "Capstone, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 13)